import { Quiz } from '../../types';

const ClothingQuiz: Quiz[] = [
  {
    description: 'Co je tato položka?',
    name: 'Oblečení',
    questions: [
      {
        answer: ['tshirt'],
        question: 'tričko'
      },
      {
        answer: ['shirt'],
        question: 'košile'
      },
      {
        answer: ['blouse'],
        question: 'blůza'
      },
      {
        answer: ['hat'],
        question: 'klobouk'
      },
      {
        answer: ['cap'],
        question: 'kšiltovka'
      },
      {
        answer: ['trousers', 'pants'],
        question: 'kalhoty'
      },
      {
        answer: ['jeans'],
        question: 'džíny'
      },
      {
        answer: ['socks'],
        question: 'ponožky'
      },
      {
        answer: ['hoody', 'sweatshirt'],
        question: 'mikina'
      },
      {
        answer: ['dress'],
        question: 'šaty'
      },
      {
        answer: ['skirt'],
        question: 'sukně'
      },
      {
        answer: ['shorts'],
        question: 'šortky'
      },
      {
        answer: ['shoes'],
        question: 'boty'
      },
      {
        answer: ['sandals'],
        question: 'sandály'
      },
      {
        answer: ['slippers'],
        question: 'pantofle'
      },
      {
        answer: ['sneakers'],
        question: 'botasky'
      },
      {
        answer: ['bowtie'],
        question: 'motýlek'
      },
      {
        answer: ['tie'],
        question: 'kravata'
      },
      {
        answer: ['shorts'],
        question: 'kraťasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['jacket'],
        question: 'bunda'
      },
      {
        answer: ['slippers'],
        question: 'papuče'
      },
      {
        answer: ['coat'],
        question: 'kabat'
      },
      {
        answer: ['gloves'],
        question: 'rukavice'
      },
      {
        answer: ['scarf'],
        question: 'šála'
      },
      {
        answer: ['underwear'],
        question: 'spodní prádlo'
      },
      {
        answer: ['sweater'],
        question: 'svetr'
      },
    ]
  }
];

export default ClothingQuiz;
